Here’s how to add a new Web Panel in Vivaldi
To get started, expand the main Panel by clicking the Show Panel toggle in the Status Bar.
In the expanded view, you’ll now see icons for your Bookmarks, Downloads, and Notes.
Below that, there is a “plus” sign which can be used to add new Web Panels.
Click this plus sign, enter the URL for the site you’d like to add, and hit Enter.
You’re new panel is live - and will be ready
for you
whenever you relaunch the browser or open a new window.
Web Panels are a great way to keep up with social feeds and messenger apps throughout the day,
or to quickly access tools that you find yourself visiting regularly.
Any page can be added as a Web Panel.
Simply open the page you’d like to add, right-click anywhere
and select “Add Page to Web Panel” from the menu.
Keep in mind that due to the smaller view area, mobile-friendly sites will work best.
Thanks for watching.
Find out more by visiting vivaldi.com